We're creating gift baskets and this theme is about chocolate.
I've put together a bunch of different items as we'll call recipes to go into the basket.
What we've done is we've put together things that have to do with chocolate or that will compliment chocolate.
You don't always have to stick to everything chocolate.
But to start with, we found a really neat chocolate lovers cookbook and we thought that would be a lot of fun because there will be all kinds of recipes in there to play with.
Then we thought we'd put together some hot chocolate ideas.
Here's a group of three and this one is really neat.
Peppermint as well as the other flavors and that's kind of different.
You'll find that stores like Roth's and TJ Maxx as well as a World Market, if you have one of those in your neighborhood; they've usually got a lot of good selections of things from all over the world so you get some good ideas in there.
So let me put that in.
Barney's always has a good selection of hot chocolate and flavors.
Here's a French vanilla and gingerbread, and they can go in.
And I think it's fun putting together things that compliment as well as just other things that you know the person would like, for example, here's an original maple syrup and that's good for somebody with a sweet tooth so we thought we'd put that in.
Here's another flavor that compliments chocolate really well and I found these key lime cookies in Roth's as well.
Sometimes in the stores in the Keys in Florida, you'll find these.
Key lime goes really well with chocolate.
Then I found one of these festive tins and that's really neat and they can be reused as well.
In here, I put a lot of the Lyndore chocolates and they're really good because they're already individually wrapped and there's a variety of flavors too, white and milk and dark chocolate so that's neat and I put a lot of them in here and then as well, I saved some out so that we can just toss them over at the end and that will look pretty.
Then not only for kids, but sometimes adults like little characters as well and here's another flavor that compliments chocolate as well, peppermint.
So we'll put her in there.
Then we found of course, Cadbury's.
You couldn't have a chocolate basket without something from Cadbury's.
We found another hot chocolate mix and we'll put that in.
And of course we've got our festive mug to go, put our hot chocolate in, it's an elephant, he's kind of cute.
And a piesta resistance is Godiva liquor.
They've got different flavors as well, milk chocolate, dark chocolate and white.
I've chosen dark for this one.
So there we have different ideas of things you can put together for your chocolate theme.
We'll get together in the next segment and we'll see how to put them all together.
Catch up with you.